buffalo-technology.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy policy - Buffalo Technology

## BUFFALO EU B.V. – Privacy

  1. Introduction This privacy policy (“Policy”) provides information and obligations on the personal data processing by Buffalo EU B.V. in the Netherlands, a private company with limited liability established under Dutch law, having its statutory seat in Amsterdam, and is registered with the Dutch trade register of the Chamber of Commerce under number 34299135 (hereinafter referred to as: “Buffalo”): 

Buffalo can be contacted via one of the following means: 

Buffalo EU B.V. Saturnusstraat 17 2132 HB Hoofddorp Email: privacybuffalo@buffalo-technology.com Telephone: +31 (0)23 5546010 Chamber of Commerce registration no. 34299135  
VAT No: NL819264957B01 

Buffalo is part of Buffalo Inc. and Melco Holdings Inc., with its headquarters in Nagoya, Japan.

Buffalo reserves the right to review and/or alter the Policy periodically, in order to comply with (local and/or European) legislation, and for any other purpose deemed reasonably necessary by Buffalo. For queries and inquiries about this Policy, please contact our Privacy policy contact person at privacybuffalo@buffalo-technology.com 

  2. Handling of Personal Data Buffalo is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Policy sets out the elements necessary for Buffalo’s compliance with applicable privacy legislation, principles and practice, including but not limited to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (“applicable laws”). This Policy explains how and for what purpose Buffalo uses the information that identify or may identify a natural person (“Personal Data”) collected from the website www.buffalo-technology.com (referred to in the rest of this Policy as the “Website”). Please read this Policy carefully.

The Policy is an external policy, and is directed towards external parties who’s Personal Data is being processed by Buffalo (“you” or “Data Subjects”).This Policy applies to the processing of Personal Data, in which Buffalo acts as the data controller, within the meaning of the applicable laws. This is the case when Buffalo determines the purpose and the means for the processing of Personal Data of parties.

For business purposes, you may be asked to provide your Personal Data. If this is the case, Buffalo and our partners shall be required to keep such information confidential. 

  3. Personal Data Personal Data mentioned herein and defined by Buffalo refers to information of all kinds related to each individual person that is electronically transmitted to Buffalo by you. The types of Personal Data Buffalo collects and processes include: 
    * name, 
    * email address, 
    * postal address,
    * job title, 
    * telephone number
    * IP address
    * information regarding your professional interests, 
    * your experience with our products,
    * preferences such as the type of products already sold by your organisation,
    * which manufacturers’ products your organisation already sells. 
    * newsletter articles you have expressed an interest in. 
  4. Purpose and Legal Basis of Data Processing Buffalo uses the information that it collects in order to: 
    * help you complete a transaction,
    * communicate with you, 
    * provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, and 
    * personalize and improve the Website for you. 

It is not allowed to process Personal Data beyond the legal basis on which the processing of Personal Data is based. Personal Data can be processed based on one of the following legal grounds:

Legal basis: contract Buffalo may use your Personal Data for the purpose of the performance of a contract, to which the Data Subjects are a party, and where the Personal Data are necessary to enter into a contract. Without providing the Personal Data, the contract cannot be performed. 

For this purposes, Buffalo retains the Personal Data for a period of seven (7) years after the termination date of the contract. 

Legal basis: consent On the basis of consent, Buffalo processes Personal Data for the following purpose(s):  communicate with you, and  provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.

For this purpose, Buffalo retains the Personal Data for a period of five (5) years. In case you gave your explicit consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.

Legal ground: legitimate interest On the basis of legitimate interest, Buffalo processes Personal Data for the following purpose(s):  provide you with information, products or services that we feel may interest you, and  personalize and improve the Website for you. 

For these purposes, Buffalo retains the Personal Data for a period of five (5) years.

Buffalo is obligated to process the Personal Data only in accordance with these purposes and in compliance with the applicable laws. 

Retention period Buffalo will not use and store your Personal Data longer than necessary to fulfil the abovementioned purposes, and shall remove the collected Personal Data after the necessary period to achieve the purposes described in this Policy has passed, or to comply with contractual obligations or as permitted or required by the applicable laws.

  5. Purpose Limitation The Personal Data may only be processed to the extent necessary for the above described purposes. Personal Data may in principle not be processed for other purposes other than that for which the Personal Data were collected. If Buffalo thinks there is a necessity or need to process Personal Data for other purposes, Buffalo shall investigate whether the purposes of the intended data processing is compatible with the original purposes. Buffalo shall provide you, prior to that further processing, with information on that other purpose.
  6. Security of your Personal Data Buffalo is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of Personal Data, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 
  7. Transfer of your Personal Data Your information may be accessed or transferred by Buffalo entities and other third parties as outlined in this Policy. Group entities Buffalo data is stored in the Netherlands. Personal Data may be shared with Buffalo’s group entities in compliance with applicable law, for purposes consistent with this Policy. Where Buffalo group entities qualify as Processors or Co-Controllers, Buffalo will enter into a Data Processing Agreement or Controller to Controller Agreement with them. Vendors and suppliers Buffalo occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, including service providers, (potential) business partners and project companies. Buffalo will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. In all cases, Buffalo will expressly state why such information is necessary, so that you may provide the information at your own discretion. Buffalo will not disclose Personal Data provided by parties to any party, other than Buffalo itself, without prior permission from the parties. Law enforcement purposes In certain circumstances, it is possible that Personal Data may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders. Buffalo may disclose Personal Data in case such disclosure is mandatory under applicable laws or is reasonably judged to be essential in order to protect and safeguard the rights, property and safety of other parties, Buffalo itself, and/or Buffalo’s affiliates. Sale of merger business Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Buffalo decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of Personal Data to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is Buffalo’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. Transfer of data to third countries Buffalo may transfer Personal Data to a third country or international organisations outside of the EU/EEA, such as to Buffalo Inc. headquarters in Japan, which shall take place only in compliance with the applicable laws, and where appropriate safeguards are in place that ensure the level of protection of parties as required by the applicable laws (e.g. transfers on the basis of an adequacy decision or standard EU Model clauses). These safeguards include entering into EU Model Clauses with the recipient of the Personal Data who is established outside the EU/EEA. The EU Model Clauses are attached to the Data Processing Agreement between Buffalo and its data processors. 
  8. Rights in relation to Personal Data Parties have the right of information, access, rectification, addition and erasure of Personal Data, and the right to object against or restrict the processing of Personal Data (or withdraw an earlier given consent), as well as the right to data portability. The procedure of Buffalo that enable you to exercise these rights is described below. Parties may file a request for access with Buffalo, and Buffalo shall respond as soon as possible and in any event within one (1) month, about: a) whether Buffalo holds any Personal Data relating to the respective the Data Subject; and, b) if so, information is provided on the purposes of the processing, the categories, the recipients (if applicable) the retention periods, the rights of the Data Subject, the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, the existence of automated decision-making, where the data is transferred to a third country, the appropriate safeguards and the source(s) of the Personal Data. After a party has accessed the Personal Data, he/she may request Buffalo to correct, restrict, amend, add, erase and/or transport the Personal Data. Buffalo informs the Data Subject within one (1) month after receiving the request whether the request shall be complied with (in time), and if not, accompanied with the reasons for the delay or rejection. You can exercise your rights by sending an email to privacybuffalo@buffalo-technology.com. You can exercise these rights at reasonable intervals. Information provided shall be free of charge, unless in the event of apparent misuse, in which case the reasonable (actual) costs may be charged or a request may be refused. Buffalo will comply with a legitimate request of a Data Subject for erasure or restriction if the Personal Data are factually incorrect, incomplete, or irrelevant for the purpose(s) of the data processing, or otherwise processed in violation with the applicable laws. With regard to a request to erase Personal Data, it should be taken into account that Buffalo shall not comply with such request, if it is incompatible with any legal obligations of Buffalo. If a request is allowed, Buffalo shall execute the decision to erase and/or restrict the Personal Data as soon as possible. Buffalo shall execute the requests of access, correction and/or data portability as soon as possible, at least within four weeks. In the event of concerns or complaints about the handling of Personal Data, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a local supervisory authority (in the Netherlands: Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens).
  9. Cookie Policy A ‘cookie’ is a small unit of information which can be passed to your browser while you are using the Website and/or another Buffalo website. In most cases, cookies are used to ensure an efficient use of the Website. If you do not want websites to use cookies with your browser, you may deny the cookies (this only applies for cookies for which an explicit consent is required) for the Website, and/or change the settings on your internet browser so that the cookies are deleted or deactivated. If you do not allow the use of cookies and have deactivated the cookies or arranged to have the cookies deactivated, this may have consequences for the ease of use of the Website.

The Website automatically generates log files that register the use by you and other parties of the Website. Buffalo maintains user data, such as source addresses of pages requested, IP (internet protocol) addresses and domain names, dates and times of page requests, links from other websites and other parameters in the URLs (universal resource locators). These log files and data will be used, on an anonymous basis, for statistical purposes and for improving the services offered via the Website.

With regard to the cookies that are used on the Website, Buffalo retains the abovementioned Personal Data for a period of five (5) years

  10. Questions and Inquiries For queries and inquiries about this Policy of Buffalo, please contact our Privacy policy contact person at privacybuffalo@buffalo-technology.com.
